Guide to the Ron Padgett Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Ron Padgett papers
1929-2008
YCAL MSS 721
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
87.4
(89 boxes)
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by Ron Padgett in the course of his work as a poet, translator, and editor. Material includes extensive correspondence with other poets and writers; manuscripts for Padgett's books of poetry, prose, and translations, as well as some juvenilia and early writings; and manuscripts for writings by others. Also included are "bokes," the term coined by Padgett to describe the "little unique editions" Ted Berrigan and he made for each other beginning in the 1960s, which encompass dozens of unique handmade works by Tom Clark, Anne Waldman, Bill Berkson, George Schneeman, Michael Brownstein, Larry Fagin, Tom Veitch, Aram Saroyan, Steve Carey, and Lewis Warsh, among others. Also found are notebooks, including numerous travel diaries, project notebooks, and personal journals; appointment books for the years 1971 to 2002; as well as teaching files; student papers; research material; printed material; and personal papers. The collection also contains files for White Dove Review, edited by Padgett, along with Dick Gallup and Joe Brainard, while they were high school students in Tulsa, and Full Court Press, edited and published by Padgett, Joan Simon, and Anne Waldman from 1974 to 1989.
Padgett, Ron, 1942-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Granary Books on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2009.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 89: (computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files are available. Consult Access Services for further information.
Associated Materials
Other material by or relating to Ron Padgett can be found by searching the Uncataloged Acquisitions Database and Orbis (Yale's Online Catalog).
Ron Padgett
Ron Padgett was born in Tulsa, Oklahoma in 1942. He began writing at the age of 13 and started a little magazine in high school called The White Dove Review with friends Dick Gallup and Joe Brainard. In its five issues, the magazine published Allen Ginsberg, Jack Kerouac, Robert Creeley, LeRoi Jones (now Amiri Baraka), Ted Berrigan, and others.
In 1960, he moved to New York, where he attended Columbia College and studied with Kenneth Koch and Lionel Trilling. Padgett later spent a year in Paris on a Fulbright fellowship where he studied French literature.
His first collection of poems, Bean Spasms, written with Ted Berrigan, was published in 1967. Since then he has published several books of poetry, including How to Be Perfect (Coffee House Press, 2007), You Never Know (2002), Poems I Guess I Wrote (2001), New & Selected Poems (1995), The Big Something (1990), Triangles in the Afternoon (1979), and Great Balls of Fire (1969).
He has also published a volume of selected prose titled Blood Work (1993), as well as translations of Blaise Cendrars' Complete Poems (1992), Pierre Cabanne's Dialogues with Marcel Duchamp (1971), and Guillaume Apollinaire's The Poet Assassinated (1968).
Padgett was the editor-in-chief of World Poets, a three-volume reference book (Scribner, 2000). He served as director of the St. Mark's Poetry Project from 1978 to 1980 and then was the publications director of Teachers & Writers Collaborative for twenty years. He was elected as a Chancellor of the Academy of American Poets in 2008. He lives in New York City.
Biographical note is drawn from Poets.org. More information about Padgett can be found on his website.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by Ron Padgett in the course of his work as a poet, translator, and editor. Material includes extensive correspondence with other poets and writers; manuscripts for Padgett's books of poetry, prose, and translations, as well as some juvenilia and early writings; and manuscripts for writings by others. Also included are "bokes," the term coined by Padgett to describe the "little unique editions" Ted Berrigan and he made for each other beginning in the 1960s, which encompass dozens of unique handmade works by Tom Clark, Anne Waldman, Bill Berkson, George Schneeman, Michael Brownstein, Larry Fagin, Tom Veitch, Aram Saroyan, Steve Carey, and Lewis Warsh, among others. Also found are notebooks, including numerous travel diaries, project notebooks, and personal journals; appointment books for the years 1971 to 2002; as well as teaching files; student papers; research material; printed material; and personal papers. The collection also contains files for White Dove Review, edited by Padgett, along with Dick Gallup and Joe Brainard, while they were high school students in Tulsa, and Full Court Press, edited and published by Padgett, Joan Simon, and Anne Waldman from 1974 to 1989.
Correspondents include John Ashbery, Paul Auster, Glen Baxter, Bill Berkson, Ted Berrigan, Joe Brainard, Michael Brownstein, Rudy Burckhardt, Tom Clark, Clark Coolidge, Jim Dine, Kenward Elmslie, Clayton Eshleman, Larry Fagin, Kathleen Fraser, Dick Gallup, Lyn Hejinian, Susan Howe, Alex Katz, Kenneth Koch, Ann Lauterbach, Harry Mathews, Bernadette Mayer, Alice Notley, Maureen Owen, Tom Raworth, Charles Reznikov, Ed Sanders, Aram Saroyan, George Schneeman, James Schuyler, Tony Towle, Tom Veitch, Anne Waldman, Lewis Warsh, and Trevor Winkfield, among others. Among the highlights are a complete file of correspondence between Padgett and Joe Brainard from 1962 to 1993, including Padgett's letters to Brainard which were returned to Padgett upon Brainard's death in 1994; a complete file of correspondence between Padgett and Berrigan from 1959 to 1983; and extensive correspondence from James Schuyler, as well as correspondence from Schuyler to Joe Brainard, dating from 1966 to 1990.
The White Dove Review files consist of all known correspondence and manuscripts, including those of Allen Ginsberg, Jack Kerouac, e. e. cummings, Robert Creeley, LeRoi Jones, David Meltzer, and Ron Lowinsohn, among others, and provide documentation of the magazine that helped launch Padgett's career and that influenced many of the Second Generation New York School little magazines and presses.
The Full Court Press files consist of all known correspondence, manuscripts, proofs, production material, promotion files, and business records. Writers published by Full Court include Joe Brainard, William Burroughs, Edwin Denby, Larry Fagin, Allen Ginsberg, John Godfrey, Frank O'Hara, Phillipe Soupault (William Carlos Williams, translator), and Tom Veitch.
American literature -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Publishers and publishing; Translators and translating; Poets; Ashbery, John, 1927-2017; Auster, Paul, 1947-; Baxter, Glen, 1944-; Berkson, Bill, 1939-2016; Berrigan, Ted, 1934-1983; Brainard, Joe, 1942-1994; Brownstein, Michael, 1943-; Burckhardt, Rudy; Clark, Tom, 1941-; Coolidge, Clark, 1939-; Dine, Jim, 1935-; Elmslie, Kenward, 1929-; Eshleman, Clayton; Fagin, Larry, 1937-; Fraser, Kathleen, 1935-; Gallup, Dick, 1941-; Hejinian, Lyn; Howe, Susan, 1937-; Katz, Alex, 1927-; Koch, Kenneth, 1925-2002; Lauterbach, Ann, 1942-; Mathews, Harry, 1930-2017; Mayer, Bernadette; Notley, Alice, 1945-; Owen, Maureen, 1943-; Padgett, Ron, 1942-; Raworth, Tom, 1938-; Sanders, Ed, 1939-; Saroyan, Aram, 1943-; Schneeman, George; Schuyler, James; Towle, Tony, 1939-; Veitch, Tom, 1951-; Waldman, Anne, 1945-; Warsh, Lewis, 1944-; Winkfield, Trevor, 1944-
- February 2009 Acquistion, 1929-2008; (89 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Organized into seven series: Correspondence, Writings, Notebooks and Bokes, White Dove Review, Full Court Press, Teaching Files, and Personal and Professional Papers.
  - Correspondence, 1950s-2008
    Arranged into broad groups according to location of origin or storage: Living Room Top Shelf; Manhattan Ministorage; and Vermont. Some outgoing correspondence is arranged as a group at the end. Outgoing correspondence can also be found intermingled with incoming correspondence in other groups.
    Correspondence has not been arranged or sorted within boxes and folders.
    General note
    Includes lists of correspondents from dealer list, when available. The best way to locate correspondence from a particular individual is to do a keyword search by name.
    - Living Room Top Shelf
      - Charles Reznikoff and Philippe Soupault, 1970; 1980-1981 (Box 1)
      - Jackie Monnier, Man Ray and Marcel Duchamp, 1966-1970 (Box 1)
      - Bill Berkson, 1968-1971 (Box 1)
      - Harry Mathews and Maxine Groffsky, 1965-1970 (Box 1)
      - Aram Saroyan, 1967-1971 (Box 1)
      - Kenward Elmslie, 1966-1971 (Box 1)
      - Annie Waldman and Lewis Warsh, 1967-1971 (Box 1)
      - Jim Dine, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
      - Trevor Winkfield, Tom Raworth, Lee Harwood and Glen Baxter, 1966-1971 (Box 1)
      - Larry Bensky, 1966-1970; 2008; 2 (Box 1)
      - Angelica Clark and Tom Clark, 1966-1971; 3 (Box 1)
      - George Tysh and Chris Tysh, 1966-1969 (Box 1)
      - David Ball, 1969-1971 (Box 1)
      - Larry Fagin and Joan Fagin, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
      - Business, 1963-1971; 2 (Box 1)
      - Dick Gallup, 1963-1969 (Box 1)
      - Peter Schjeldahl, 1964-1967 (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous Letters, 1966-1971; 2 (Box 2)
        Scope and Contents
        Includes correspondence from:
        Edwin Denby
        Phillip Lopate
        Pat Nolan
        Bill Zavatsky
        Harris Schiff
        Lewis MacAdams
        Brassai
        Fairfield Porter
        John Ashbery
        Anselm Hollo
        Vito Acconci
        Katz
        Philip Whalen
        Joe LeSueur
        LeRoi Jones
        Joseph Ceravolo
        Barbara Guest
        F. W. Dupee, and others.
      - Tom Veitch, 1964-1971; 4 (Box 2)
      - Clark Coolidge, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
      - Tom Disch and Jim Sallis, 1968-1971 (Box 2)
      - Donald Hall, 1968-1971 (Box 2)
      - Lauren Owen and Maureen Owen, 1966-1968 (Box 2)
      - David Shapiro, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
      - Kenneth Koch, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
      - Johnny Stanton, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
      - Tony Towle, 1966-1968 (Box 2)
      - Michael Brownstein, 1967-1971 (Box 2)
      - George Schneeman and Katie Schneeman, 1966-1971 (Box 2)
      - Kay Boyle, 1964-1969 (Box 2)
      - "Anon", 1967 (Box 2)
        Contains a note sent from Tulsa, Oklahoma to Ron Padgett in 1967 when he was apartment hunting.
      - Jim Brodey, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
      - Micellaneous Letters, 1960s-1970s; 2 (Box 2)
        Glen Baxter
        Tom Clark
        Dick Gallup
        Tom Veitch
        Bill Berkson
        Clark Coolidge
        Michael Brownstein
        Anne Waldman
        Kenward Elmslie
        Lewis Warsh
        Trevor Winkfield
        South Carolina people
        Rudy Burckhardt
        George Tysh
        Tom Raworth
        Allen Ginsberg
        Jackie Monnier
        Jim Dine
        Ron Padgett
        Peter Orlovsky
        Maureen Owen
        Duncan McNaughton
        Steve Katz
        Barnett Watten
        Alice Notley
        Eric Sackheim (Mushinsha Ltd.)
        Leroy Breunig
        Steve Levine
        Rose Lesniak
        Susan Howe
        David Ball
        Unmuzzled Ox
        Ron Shapiro
        Ed Leites
        Phyllis Rosser
        Jim Hanson
        Clayton Eshleman
        Art Lange
        Ed Sanders
        Dean Faulwell
        Richard Friedman
        Other letters and cards
        Personal and Family
      - Miscellaneous Letters (continued), 1960s-1970s; 2 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous Letters, 1976-1979; 16 (Box 3)
        Hayden Carruth
        Bill Corbett
        Serge Fauchereau
        Larry Fagin
        Susan Noel
        Harry Mathews
        Lita Hornick
        David Shapiro
        Anne Porter
        George Schneeman
        Katie Schneeman
        Paul and Elio Schneeman
        Bernard Delvaille
        Rory McEwen
        Ted Greenwall
        Alex Katz
        Donald Allen
        Kenneth Koch
        Bill Katz
        Charles North
        Bob Cornfield
        Jim Brodey
        Ann Lauterbach
        Bob Holman
        Dale Herd
        Terrence Winch
        Ken Mikolowski
        Mary Ferrari
        Paul Violi
        Lisa Nunez
        Lyn Hejinian
        Dick Barnes
        Karl Torok
        Walter Abish (and Paris R. Wm Gass)
        MS mag (Rosser)
        Family and Friends
        Re: Literary Business
      - German Letters, 1968-1971 (Box 3)
      - Rory McEwen; Ron Padgett to Tom Veitch, 1971 (Box 3)
      - Letters Received, Various People, 1979-1981; 4 (Box 3)
        Ted Berrigan
        Aram Saroyan
        Nicole Ball
        Keith Cohen
        Yvonne Jacquette
        Morris Golde
        Reed Bye
        Gianfranco Palmery
        Charles Wright
        Michael Palmer
        Bobbie Louise Hawkins
        Living Room top shelf
        Carol Gallup
        Monique Chefdor
        Gerard-Georges Lemaire
        Jacqueline Cahen
        Alex Katz and Ada Katz
        Clark Collidge
        Paul Hoover
        Maxine Chernoff
        Alan Bernheimer
        Charles Bernstein
        Jacques Danos
        Michael Davidson
        Michel Deguy
        Steven DiLauro
        Leonard Gontarek
        Chuck Goldman
        Louise Hamline
        Robert Kelly
        Katherine Koch
        Gary Lenhart
        David Lusterman
        Ann Mikolowski
        Bernadette Mayer
        Douglas Messerli
        Paul Murphy
        J. Phillip O'Hara
        Claibe Rilchardson
        Carl Sagan
        Angelica Savinio
        Elio Schneeman
        Peter Schjeldahl
        Joan Simon
        Alex Smith
        Jean-Francois Thibault
        Michele Thomas
        Rick Winston
        Barry Yourgrau
        Dave Morice
        Gregory Kolovakos
        T.C. Marshall
        Kenneth Funsten
        Reagan Upshaw
        Jack Skelly
        Mary Wylie Robinson
        Rachel Waldrop
        David Gascoyne
        Various literary business letters
      - Letters Received, Various People (continued), 1979-1981; 4 (Box 4)
      - Tom Veitch (plus others), 1967-1981; 7 (Box 4)
        Ted Berrigan to Tom Veitch
        Uli Becker-German to Tom Veitch
        Antlers in the Treetops
      - "Mostly Tom Clark", 1966-1988 (Box 5)
    - James Schuyler / Joe Brainard / Ted Berrigan / Alice Notley / Kenward Elmslie / Gallup correspondence
      - James Schuyler to Ron and Pat Padgett, 1966-1988; 2 (Box 5)
      - James Schuyler to Joe Brainard, 1964-1990; 6 (Box 5)
      - Ted Berrigan, 1965-1970 (Box 5)
        Related Archival Materials note
        See also: Writings, Ted Berrigan, Box 58.
        Includes correspondence between Ted Berrigan and Sandy Berrigan.
      - Ted Berrigan to Ron Padgett, 1959-1983 (Box 5)
      - Ron and Pat Padgett to Ted and Sandy Berrigan - Paris, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
      - Ron Padgett to Ted Berrigan, 1961-1982 (Box 5)
      - Ted Berrigan to Ron Padgett - historical package, 1964-1971 (Box 6)
      - Ron Padgett to Ted Berrigan (from Tulsa, Vermont and New York), 1964-1968; 2 (Box 6)
      - Ted Berrigan postcards, 1960s (Box 6)
      - Miscellaneous Letters, 1959-1960 (Box 6)
      - Ron Padgett and Dick Gallup, 1960s (Box 6)
      - Alice Notley, 1970s-1980s (Box 6)
      - Kenward Elmslie, 1960s-1990s (Box 6)
      - Joe Brainard / Ron Padgett, 1950s-1990s; 6 (Box 6)
      - Joe Brainard / Ron Padgett (continued), 1950s-1990s; 9 (Box 7)
    - Manhattan Ministorage
      - Correspondence Received, 1970s-1990s; 4 (Box 7)
        Includes business and personal correspondence, as well as postcards, Christmas cards and Email printouts.
      - Correspondence Received (continued), 1970s-1990s; 3 (Box 8)
      - Correspondence Received, 1995-1996; 8 (Box 8)
        Includes letters and postcards.
      - "Correspondence Received: ABC-1", 1976-1977; 6 (Box 9)
        Includes correspondence dealing with South Carolina Writer-in-the-Community,Tap Journal, South Carolina friends, poetry business and the Full Court Press.
      - "Correspondence Received: ABC-2", 1976-1977; 5 (Box 9)
        Bill Barrett
        William Higginson
        Eileen Myles
        Rochelle Ratner
        James Grauerholz
        Rackstraw Downes
        Edmund Leites
        Rudy Burkhardt
        Chris Tysh
        Ron Loewinsohn
        David Pollens (rented Padgett NY apartment)
        Lee Sokol
        Bob Rosenthal
        Annabel Levitt
        David Rosenberg broadside
        Dennis Cooper
        Jim Thompson
        MMS
        Bruce Boone
        The Cattle Report
        F. T. Prince
        Juliet Man Ray
        Donald Hall
        Neil Welliver
        Gallery, readings annoucements, etc.
        Correspondence, June-Dec 1977
      - "Correspondence Received: ABC-3", 1977; 6 (Box 10)
        South Carolina Writer-in-the Community and South Carolina friends
        Poetry "business"
        Copy of masters thesis on Ron Padgett and David Shapiro, "The Absurd and the Abstract in New York Poetry - On the Work of Ron Padgett and David Shapiro," by Michael J. Simon, 1977.
        Lee Harwood
        Jim Wanless
        James Sherry
        Marjorie Perloff
        Frances LeFevre
        Steven Hall
        Tony Towle
        Nick Dorsky
        Don Hall
        Johnny Stanton
        David Pollens
        copy of Opera a play by Frank O'Hara
      - Letters, etc. Received, 1996-2001; 5 (Box 10)
        Includes letters, reading annoucements and postcards.
      - Letters, etc. Received (continued), 1996-2001; 11 (Box 11)
      - Letters, etc. Received (continued), 1996-2001; 3 (Box 12)
      - London - Cambridge, 2003 (Box 12)
        See also Manuscripts by Others
    - Manhattan Ministorage
      - Mail Received, 1997; 7 (Box 12)
        Includes approximately 100 loose letters and postcards from:
        88 invitations, annoucements, obits, catalogues including a copy of "Death & Fame" by Allen Ginsberg
        Poetry Project
        Re: Publication
        Ron Padgett grant
        Fdn. for Contemporary Perf. Arts
        Re: Requests for help, thank-yous
        Atlantic Ctr for the Arts
        Lyman Gilmore-New England College
        On Paper
        Seminary Co-op Bkstore
        Fred Villegas (Brochure for tennis friend)
        Naropa Institute
        Scholastic-Sarah Fewster
        Re: Saginaw Residency
        Saginaw Community Enrichment Commission
        Carol Scott
        Al Helles
        Postcards
        Meri & Flutura (Albania)
        David & Nicole Ball
        Shelley Lustig
        David Lehman
        George Schneeman & Katie Schneeman
        Rich & Andrea Winston
        John Brainard
        Bertrand Dorny
        Greta Goetz
        Geoff Young
        Susan Ohaiar
        Michael Leddy
        John McGraw
        Key Ransone
        David Kherdian
        Leo Edelstein
        Michael Gizzi
        Maxine (Chernoff probably, Groffsky maybe)
        Andy Christ
        Simon Kilmurry
        Abigail Susik
        Charles Graef
        Nancy Koepke
        Griffin Hamburg
      - Mail Received, 1997 (Box 12)
        Includes approximately 45 loose letters and postcards, as well as 200 larger letters and other correspondence from:
        Archie Rand drawing note
        Robert Pensky
        Paul Violil
        Mac McGinnes
        Jay Bochner
        George Schneeman and Katie Schneeman (G. drawing w/R. writing)
        Nathan Kernan
        Keith McDermott
        Jean Boult Lge card of Boult photo
        Anne Walker
        Geof Hewitt
        Frederic Inigo
        Elspeth & Bill Carnahan
        Kenward Elmslie Special Cards and Post Cards
        James Jaffe bks
        John Brainard fax
        David Burgess
        Susan Coolidge
        Penny Harter & William Higginson
        Vivien Elmslie
        Sandy Berrigan
        David Berrigan
        Tom & Val Raworth
        Frank Lima
        Ken Bolton (Otis Rush) Photo
        Connie Deanovich
        Bill Bamberger
        Lois Eby
        Ed Foster
        F. Richard Thomas
        Kelby Garfield
        Griffin Hansberry
        Justin Leites
        Howard Brainard
        Lynda Chin
        Bobbie West
        Arthur Tobier
        Timothy Baum Soupault
        Tim Hather
        M. Gorelick (Sparrow)
        James Levinson
        Tim O'Flynn
        Brad Leithauser
        Betim Muco
        The Mikolowskis Calendar w/ art by Ann
      - Mail Received (continued), 1997; 4 (Box 13)
      - Mail Received, 1998; 8 (Box 13)
        Includes approximately 300 loose letters and postcards.
      - Email Sent and Received, 1996-1997; 8 (Box 14)
        Includes approximately 700 pages of emails.
      - Email Sent and Received, 1998; 11 (Box 14)
        Includes approximately 600 pages of printed email messages.
      - Email Sent and Received, 1998; 5 (Box 14)
        Includes approximately 450 pages of printed email messages, dating from September 1998 to December 1998.
      - Email Sent and Received (continued), 1998; 3 (Box 15)
      - Email Received, 1999; 7 (Box 15)
        Includes approximately 500 pages of printed email messages, dating from January 1999 to September 1999.
      - Email Sent, 1999; 8 (Box 15)
        Includes approximately 600 pages of printed email messages, dating from February 1999 to September 1999.
      - Email Received, 1999-2000; 6 (Box 15)
      - Email Received (continued), 1999-2000; 2 (Box 16)
      - Email Sent, 1999-2000; 7 (Box 16)
        Includes approximately 450 pages of printed email messages.
    - Vermont, 1965-2004
      - Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1970s; 8 (Box 16)
        Includes approximately 120 letters and 200 postcards from:
        Ian Hamilton Finlay
        Maxine Groffsky
        R. B. Kitaj
        and others
      - Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1975-1977; 6 (Box 17)
        Includes approximately 250 letters from:
        Thomas M. Disch
        David Antin
        Tom Mandel
        James Laughlin
        Ted Greenwald
        Red Grooms
      - Letters Received, 1978-1981; 3 (Box 17)
        Bob Perelman
        Paul Auster
        Gervais Jassaud
        F. W. Dupee
        and others.
      - Letters Received (continued), 1978-1981; 5 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1979-1981; 4 (Box 18)
        Includes approximately 200 letters from:
        Howard Norman
        Ada Katz
        Neil Baldwin
        Jean-Hubert Martin
        Andrei Codrescu
        Dick Higgins
      - Miscellaneous Letters Received (continued), 1979-1981; 3 (Box 19)
      - Letters Received, 1980s; 5 (Box 19)
        Includes approximately 100 letters and postcards from:
        Kay Boyle
        Bruce Weber
        Stephen Ratcliffe
      - Letters Received, 1985; 3 (Box 19)
        Includes approximately 100 letters and 100 postcards from:
        Clayton Eschleman
        Ed Ruscha
        David Rattray
        Mortimer Guiney
        Ellie Dorfman
      - Letters Received (continued), 1985; 3 (Box 20)
      - Letters, Etc., 1985-1988; 7 (Box 20)
        Includes approximately 13 letters from Ron Padgett, as well as 200 letters and postcards from:
        Jeffrey Harrison
      - Received in Vermont, 1980s-1995; 7 (Box 21)
        Includes approximately 200 letters and postcards received in Vermont from:
        Brad Morrow
        George Schneeman and Katie Schneeman
        Joan Brix Banks
        Steve Rodefer
        Jack Collom
        Paul Cummings
        Douglas Dunn
        Robert Creeley
        Joan Acocella
        Michael Friedman
        Reva Wolf
      - Correspondence Received, 1980s; 3 (Box 21)
        Includes approximately 250 letters and postcards from:
        Peter Gizzi
        Clayton Eshlemann
        Jonathan Cott
        Robert Cornfield
      - Correspondence Received (continued), 1980s; 4 (Box 22)
      - Correspondence Received, 1990; 6 (Box 22)